Guide to the St. Paul's United Methodist Church records, 1821-2009.
St. Paul's United Methodist Church records, 1821-2009.
- Central N. Y. Annual Conference Minutes, 1891; Pamphlets (Unbound) (Box 31)
- Central N. Y. Annual Conference Minutes, 1892; Pamphlets (Unbound) (Box 31)
- Central N. Y. Annual Conference Minutes, 1893; Pamphlets (Unbound) (Box 31)
- Central N. Y. Annual Conference Minutes, 1897-1932; Pamphlets (Unbound) (Box 32)
- Central N. Y. Annual Conference Minutes, 1933-1953; Pamphlets (Unbound) (Box 33)
- Central N. Y. Annual Conference Hear Book, 1954-1963; Pamphlets (Unbound) (Box 34)
- Quarterly Conference Minutes and Accounts of Aurora St., 1844-1871; Manuscript Volume (Box 34)
- Minutes of Quaterly Conference, 1871-1890; Manuscript Volume (Box 34)
- Minutes of Quaterly Conference, 1890-1907; Manuscript Volume (Box 34)
- Quaterly Conference Minutes, 1913-1938; Manuscript Volume (Box 35)
- Quaterly Conference Minutes, 1907-1915; Manuscript Volume (Box 36)
- Quaterly Conference Minutes, 1939-1949; MS., types & Mimeo. (Box 36)
- The Fourth Quarterly Conference, 1946; Mimeo Volume (Box 36)
- The Fourth Quarterly Conference, 1947; Mimeo Volume (Box 36)
- The Fourth Quarterly Conference, 1948; Mimeo Volume (Box 36)
- The Fourth Quarterly Conference, 1949; Mimeo Volume (Box 36)
- Official Quarterly Conference Record, 1949-1950; Soft Cover Mimeo. (Box 37)
  Quaterly Conference Misc.
- The Annual Meeting of First M. E., 1950; Soft Cover Mimeo. (Box 37)
- The Annual Meeting of First M. E., 1951; Soft Cover Mimeo. (Box 37)
- The Annual Meeting of First M. E., 1953; Soft Cover Mimeo. (Box 37)
- The Annual Meeting of First M. E., 1954; Soft Cover Mimeo. (Box 37)
- The Annual Meeting of First M. E., 1955; Soft Cover Mimeo. (Box 37)
- The Annual Meeting of First M. E., 1956; Soft Cover Mimeo. (Box 37)
- Directory of the State Street M. E. Church, 1892; Pamphlets (Box 37)
  History, Misc. Pamphlets
- 1907-04-28 (Box 37)
- Directory of the State Street M. E. Church, 1917-1923; Pamphlets (Box 37)
- Centennial of First M. E. Church, 1920; Pamphlets (Box 37)
- 1939 (Box 37)
- 1939, Pamphlets (Box 37)
- 1941-02, Typescript (Box 37)
- Address 125th Anniversary of Founding of First M. E. by John G. Brooks, 1944; Typescript (Box 37)
- 1838-10-19 (Box 37)
- Zion's Herald and Wesleyan Journal (Boston Wesleyan Association: Boston), 1953-04-27; Newspapers (Box 37)
- Clipping - Rutland Herald (E. Maxim: Rutland, Vermont), 1831-04-26; Newspapers (Box 37)
- Syracuse Reveille - Clipping, Undated; Newspapers (Box 37)
- Ithaca Journal Centennial Number, 1915; Newspapers (Box 37)
- Natural Coarse Fabric Bound Volume of Chancelline Drawings, Undated; Newspapers (Box 37)
  Detail Perspective, Plan, Longitudinal Section. Signed by Wurster McNeill Baker
- Pastboard Sign with the Lettering: I'D LOVE TO, Undated; Newspapers (Box 37)
- Daily Christian Advocate (Philadelphia), 1864-05-03-1864-05-28; Large Bound Volume Newspaper (Box 37)
- Gallery, Sanctuary, Ground, Mezzanine Floor Plans, Undated (Folder 1)
- Floor, Ground, and Roof Plans of Garage for First Methodist Church, Undated (Folder 1)
- Cross Section, Longitudinal Section of Garage, Undated (Folder 1)
- Preliminary Drawings Chancel and Chapel Plans, Chancel Elevation First Methodist Church, 1944-06-12 (Folder 1)
- Blueprint Chancel and Chapel Plans, Chancel Elevation, 1944-06-13 (Folder 1)
- Coloured Drawing of Chancel Elevation, Undated (Folder 1)